Guide to the Herman F. Mark Collection RG.002
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VI: Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn and the Polymer Research Institute
  - Subseries A: Mark Birthday Symposia and Festschrift
    - 70th Birthday Symposium invitations, 1965; cuid3210 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - 70th Birthday Symposium program, seating, and notes, 1965; cuid3211 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 70th Birthday Symposium press release and photo, 1965; cuid3212 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 70th Birthday Symposium publications photocopies, 1965; cuid3213 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 75th Birthday Tribute- Herman Mark Chair Established, 1970; cuid3214 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Herman F. Mark Chair in Polymer Science, 1970 May 3; cuid3215 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Drive for Mark Chair Picks up Steam" article with 80th Birthday Symposium program, 1975; cuid3216 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 80th Birthday Banquet programs, 1975; cuid3217 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 80th Birthday planning and invitation list, 1974; cuid3218 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - 80th Birthday thank you cards, 1975; cuid3219 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - 80th Birthday newspaper clippings, 1975; cuid3220 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - The Herman F. Mark Chair in Polymer Science pamphlets, 1979; cuid3221 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - 85th Birthday Symposium "Polymers in the Service of Man", 1980; cuid3222 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Golden Anniversary Symposium: Celebrating the 50th Anniversary of the Ph.D. Program in Chemistry and the Birthdays of Herman Mark (90), Frederich Eirich (80), Herbert Morazwetz (70), 1985; cuid3223 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 90th Birthday Symposium "Polymer Science in the Next Decade" invitations and program, 1985; cuid3224 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - 90th Birthday newspaper clippings and articles, 1985; cuid3225 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - 90th Birthday Symposium review, 1985; cuid3226 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - 90th Birthday letters and cards, 1985; cuid3227 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - 90th Birthday letters and cards, 1985; cuid3228 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - 90th Birthday letters and cards, 1985; cuid3229 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - 90th Birthday telegrams, 1985; cuid3230 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - 90th Birthday Symposium photographs, 1985; cuid3231 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - 95th Birthday Symposium program and ticket, 1990; cuid3232 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - 95th Birthday Symposium planning and invitation lists, 1990; cuid3233 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - 95th Birthday Symposium correspondence, 1990; cuid3234 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - 95th Birthday Symposium opening lecture draft, 1990; cuid3235 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - 96th Birthday letters, 1991; cuid3236 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - "Portrait of a Scientist: Twenty minutes of time in his office" by L. Schleiniger, 1976 January; cuid3237 (Box 20, Item 1)
    - Birthday gift "Natur und Architektur", 1985; cuid3238 (Box 20, Item 2)
    - Birthday wishes from Mayor Koch (bound), 1985 May 6; cuid3239 (Box 20, Item 3)
    - Birthday wishes from The Association of Finnish Chemical Societies (bound), 1985 May 3; cuid3240 (Box 20, Item 4)
    - Grosse Goldene Ehrenzeichen mit dem Stern [Great Golden medal with Star] awarded by the Republic of Austria (in red binder with gold seal), 1985 April 22; cuid3241 (Box 20, Item 5)
    - 70th Birthday Celebration photo album, 1965 May; cuid3242 (Box 20, Item 6)
    - "Perspective in Polymer Science: A Volume dedicated to Herman F. Mark on the occasion of his 70th birthday" ed. E. Proskauer, E. Immergut, C. Overberger, 1966; cuid3243 (Box 20, Item 7)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from The Polish Academy of Sciences: Centre of Molecular and Marcomolecular Studies (bound), 1985 April 12; cuid3244 (Box 20, Item 8)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from Die Österreichische Akademie der Wissenschaften [the Austrian Academy of Sciences], 1985 May 3; cuid3245 (Box 20, Item 9)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from the Chinese Chemical Society member and former student Qian Baogong, 1985; cuid3246 (Box 20, Item 10)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from the Chinese Chemical Society President Qian Renyuan, 1985 May; cuid3247 (Box 20, Item 11)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from the Chinese Chemical Society member Liu Dagang, 1985 May; cuid3248 (Box 20, Item 12)
    - 90th Birthday Festschrift from the Institute of Macromolecular Chemistry, Czechoslovak Academy of Science, 1985; cuid3249 (Box 20, Item 13)
    - "Polymer Science in the Next Decade: An International Symposium Honoring Herman F. Mark on his 90th Birthday" ed. O Vogl and E. Immergut, 1987; cuid3250 (Box 20, Item 14)
  - Subseries B: Mark Memorial Symposium and Scholarship Fund
    - Memorial Symposium planning materials (including photographs), 1992; cuid3251 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Symposium planning materials (S.M. Atlas), 1992; cuid3252 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Symposium "Polymers to the Year 2000 and Beyond" programs and booklets, 1992; cuid3253 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Symposium invitation lists and registration forms, 1992; cuid3254 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Symposium invitation lists and registration forms, 1992; cuid3255 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Symposium invitations and registration forms, 1992; cuid3256 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Symposium fax confirmation slips, 1992; cuid3257 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Mark Scholarship Fund donor lists, 1992; cuid3258 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Mark Scholarship Fund donor lists, 1992; cuid3259 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Mark Symposium and Fund thank you lists, 1992; cuid3260 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Memorial Symposium manuscripts and Wiley correspondence, 1992; cuid3261 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Subseries C: Events
    - Polymer Research Institute Symposia programs, 1949-1989; 1949-1966; cuid3262 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Symposia brochures, 1948-1967; cuid3263 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Symposium-Workshop, "Polymeric Materials and their use in Transportation," and project proposals, 1976-1977; cuid3264 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - "Polymer Synthesis in the 1980s" Symposium and Honorary Degree awarded to Prof. Carl S. Marvel, cuid3265 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Symposium in Memorial of Professor Aharon Katzir-Katchalsky, 1973 February 3; cuid3266 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Event Programs, 1966-1968; cuid3267 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Subseries D: News and Brochures
    - PRI and Polytechnic public relations, 1961-2003; 1961-1968; cuid3268 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases, 1960-1966; cuid3269 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Report from Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1955-1956; cuid3270 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Polytechnic in Brief and Polytechnic News, 1968-2003; cuid3271 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - The Polytechnic Faculty News, 1957-1971; 1965-1971; cuid3272 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - PRI and Polytechnic brochures, 1960s - 2000s; cuid3273 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Series VII: Photographs
  - Subseries A: Portraits
    - Herman Mark in Austrian officer's uniform, World War I, undated; cuid3274 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Herman Mark in Rogers Hall office, undated; cuid3275 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Herman Mark black and white portraits, undated; cuid3276 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Herman Mark black and white portraits, undated; cuid3277 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Herman Mark black and white portraits, undated; cuid3278 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Herman Mark color portraits, undated; cuid3279 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Herman Mark silhouette portrait, undated; cuid3280 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Herman Mark black and white portraits with contact sheet, undated; cuid3281 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Herman Mark color portrait contact sheet, 1975; cuid3282 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Herman Mark black and white portraits with negatives, undated; cuid3283 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Herman Mark portrait photocopies, undated; cuid3284 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Herman Mark Oversize portrait, undated; cuid3285 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - Subseries B: Family and Friends
    - Portraits and group photos, 1927-1929; undated; cuid3286 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Family portrait reproductions (photograph, slide, photocopy), undated; cuid3287 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Group military portrait and negative, undated; cuid3288 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Maria Mark (Mimi), 1938; undated; cuid3289 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Herman and Maria Mark with friends, 1953, 1958; cuid3290 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Hans Mark, Peter Mark, and Mark grandchildren, undated; cuid3291 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Herman Mark with grandson Rufus and family, 1990; cuid3292 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Family and Friends, 1990s; cuid3293 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Family and Friends in Texas, 1990s; cuid3294 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Subseries C: Students and Colleagues
    - Israeli President Ephraim Katzir, 1976; undated; cuid3295 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Professor Frederick Eirich, undated; cuid3296 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Professor Murray Goodman, 1974 January 17; cuid3297 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Jack B. Nagler (former student), 1991 August 27; cuid3298 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Lingyu He (visiting scholar), 1990; cuid3299 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Bruno Zimm and Paul Doty, 1990; cuid3300 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Mark in his office and lab with colleagues, 1980s; cuid3301 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Professional associates, undated; cuid3302 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Mark with Students (includes negatives), undated; cuid3303 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Subseries D: Events
    - Herman Mark Bust dedication, with sculptor Jimilu Mason, 1959; cuid3304 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - American Chemical Society meetings, 1968, undated; cuid3305 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Willard Gibbs Medal, 1975; cuid3306 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - National Medal of Science, with President Jimmy Carter, 1979; cuid3307 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wolf Prize, 1979; cuid3308 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Heity Foundation Dinner, 1991; cuid3309 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 100 Shares of Montecatini stock to PIB, undated; cuid3310 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 80th Birthday Celebration contact sheets, 1975; cuid3311 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 90th Birthday Celebration, 1985; cuid3312 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Birthday Celebrations, miscellaneous, undated; cuid3313 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Polyethylene Demonstration, undated; cuid3314 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lectures, undated; cuid3315 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Events, miscellaneous (black and white), 1947-1986; cuid3316 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Events, miscellaneous (color), 1983; undated; cuid3317 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Subseries E: Miscellaneous
    - Travels, 1956-1966, cuid3318 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Travels, 1980-1984, cuid3319 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Mountains, undated; cuid3320 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Herman and Maria Mark's gravestone, 1992; cuid3321 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - NASA, 1976-1982; cuid3322 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Subseries F: Negatives
    - Negatives, undated; cuid3323 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Negatives, undated; cuid3324 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Subseries G: Albums
    - OMV Aktiengesellschaft, undated; cuid3325 (Box 23.5, Item 1)
    - Award reception, undated; cuid3326 (Box 23.5, Item 2)
    - Poly event, undated; cuid3327 (Box 23.5, Item 3)
  - Subseries H: Slides, undated
    - Bio, undated; cuid3328 (Box 24, Object 1)
    - CGO, undated; cuid3329 (Box 24, Object 2)
    - China, undated; cuid3330 (Box 24, Object 3)
    - China CCCP, undated; cuid3331 (Box 24, Object 4)
    - Comfort, undated; cuid3332 (Box 24, Object 5)
    - Comp, undated; cuid3333 (Box 24, Object 6)
    - Fibers Res., undated; cuid3334 (Box 24, Object 7)
    - For Peter 80th, undated; cuid3335 (Box 24, Object 8)
    - Herman K (empty box), undated; cuid3336 (Box 24, Object 9)
    - [illegible] History USA, undated; cuid3337 (Box 24, Object 10)
    - Luiz Schleiniger- Photographer, undated; cuid3338 (Box 24, Object 11)
    - Medical, undated; cuid3339 (Box 24, Object 12)
    - Medical Reserve, undated; cuid3340 (Box 24, Object 13)
    - Novophalt, undated; cuid3341 (Box 24, Object 14)
    - Perkin Ivitrene, cuid3342 (Box 24, Object 15)
    - Peter Color, 1958; cuid3343 (Box 24, Object 16)
    - Photos, undated; cuid3344 (Box 24, Object 17)
    - Supra, undated; cuid3345 (Box 24, Object 18)
    - Synthetic Paper, undated; cuid3346 (Box 24, Object 19)
- Series VIII: Framed photographs and documents
  - Subseries A: Framed Items
    - The Jabotinsky Centennial Medal, 1980-11-11; cuid3347 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 1)
    - 30 Years of International Cellulose Research Limited, 1969; cuid3348 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 2)
    - International Award in Plastics Science and Engineering, 1962; cuid3429 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 3)
    - Tree Dedication Certificate, 1983; cuid3431 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 4)
    - Journal of Polymer Research replica of cover of inaugural issue, 1985; cuid3433 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 5)
    - Family Crest, undated; cuid3435 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 6)
    - German Certificate, 1970; cuid3436 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 7)
    - Quarter Century Service Scroll, undated; cuid3438 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 8)
    - Society of Plastics Engineers, Inc. Member Emeritus, 1959; cuid3440 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 9)
    - Polymer Education Award, 1982; cuid3442 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 10)
    - Honorary Membership to The Fiber Society, 1965; cuid3443 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 11)
    - Division of Polymer Chemistry Award, 1982; cuid3444 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 12)
    - 80th Birthday Plaque from Polytechnic Institute, 1975; cuid3445 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 13)
    - Division of Cellulose Chemistry, 1959; cuid3447 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 14)
    - The Seventh Annual Plastics Planning Conference Distinguished Speaker Plaque, 1981; cuid3449 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 15)
    - Perkin Medal Award from the American Section of the Society of Chemical Industry, 1980; cuid3450 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 16)
    - Bravery Medal in 1st World War for Most Decorated Officer, undated; cuid3452 (Bin Frame Rack 1, Item 17)
    - Image of soldiers, undated; cuid3454 (Bin Folder Rack 6, Item 1)
    - Map of China, undated; cuid3455 (Bin Folder Rack 6, Item 2)
    - Framed butterfly, undated; cuid3457 (Bin Folder Rack 6, Item 3)
    - Half-Million Miler 100,000 Mile Club, undated; cuid3459 (Bin Folder Rack 6, Item 4)
    - Prof Ddr. Hermann Mark 25 Janner 1987, 1987-01-25; cuid3461 (Bin Folder Rack 6, Item 5)
    - Photograph of Herman Mark in small gold frame, undated; cuid3554 (Box 38, Item 3)
    - Photograph of four men, undated; cuid3555 (Box 38, Item 4)
    - Photograph of Herman Mark with two women, undated; cuid3556 (Box 38, Item 5)
    - Ronald Reagan photograph in Johnson Space Center, 1981-11-13; cuid3557 (Box 38, Item 6)
    - Herman Mark with unknown man photograph, undated; cuid3558 (Box 38, Item 7)
    - Group photograph from the Gordon Research Conference on Polymers, 1965-02-01-1965-02-05; cuid3559 (Box 38, Item 8)
    - Herman Mark graduation group photograph with JFK, 1961; cuid3560 (Box 38, Item 9)
  - Subseries B: Unframed Items
    - Dark wooden box HFM, Undated; cuid3430 (Box 39)
    - Scroll holder with Greek lettering, Undated; cuid3432 (Box 39)
    - Decorative wooden box, Undated; cuid3434 (Box 39)
    - Stone candle holder, Undated; cuid3437 (Box 39)
    - Stefan Meyer medal, Undated; cuid3439 (Box 39)
    - Herman F. Mark empty folder, Undated; cuid3441 (Box 39)
    - Technion-Israel Institute of Technology and The American Technion Society Harvey Prize, 1976-06-23; cuid3561 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Technion Israel Institute of Technology Honorary Degree, 1975-06-04; cuid3446 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Universitas Carolina Pragensis Honorary Degree, 1965-08-30; cuid3448 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - S.Miluera Artwork, 1975-04-15; cuid3451 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Portrait by Mimi Mark, Undated; cuid3453 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Portrait by Mimi Mark 1957, cuid3456 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Portrait by Mimi Mark 1957, cuid3458 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Portrait by Mimi Mark, Undated; cuid3460 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Portrait by Mimi Mark, Undated; cuid3462 (Bin Map Case 1)
    - Mountain Landscape, 1983-08; cuid3473 (Box 31, Item 1)
    - Photograph of Herman Mark with Herman Rudorfer, 1980-05; cuid3474 (Box 31, Item 2)
    - Herman Mark Children Photographs, undated; cuid3475 (Box 31, Item 3)
    - Charles Overberger photograph dedicated to GHR, undated; cuid3476 (Box 31, Item 4)
    - Unknown man photograph, undated; cuid3477 (Box 31, Item 5)
    - Group photograph from Herman Mark's visit to India's National Chemical Labratory, 1965-04-25; cuid3478 (Box 31, Item 6)
    - Herman Mark photograph, undated; cuid3479 (Box 31, Item 7)
    - Murray portrait dedicated to GHR, undated; cuid3480 (Box 31, Item 8)
    - Herman Mark Portrait, undated; cuid3481 (Box 31, Item 9)
    - Schlofshof au Heidelberg Photograph, undated; cuid3482 (Box 31, Item 10)
    - Professor illustration, 1982-05; cuid3483 (Box 31, Item 11)
    - Unknown woman portrait, undated; cuid3484 (Box 31, Item 12)
    - Unknown man portrait, undated; cuid3485 (Box 31, Item 13)
    - Herman Mark Portrait, undated; cuid3486 (Box 31, Item 14)
    - General Electric Certificate in Modern Engineering Fall 1962, cuid3487 (Box 32, Item 1)
    - General Electric Certificate in Modern Engineering Spring 1963, cuid3488 (Box 32, Item 2)
    - The American Chemical Society Award in Polymer Chemistry, 1965-04-05; cuid3489 (Box 32, Item 3)
    - IBM Update '77 Recognition of Participation, 1977-07-31-1977-08-26; cuid3490 (Box 32, Item 4)
    - Plastics Institute of America Recognition, 1965-01-22; cuid3491 (Box 32, Item 5)
    - Commissioning of Kentucky Colonel from Governor Brown, 1983-03-03; cuid3492 (Box 32, Item 6)
    - The Olney Medal of the American Association of Textile Chemists and Colorists, 1965; cuid3493 (Box 32, Item 7)
    - Russian Certificate, 1966; cuid3494 (Box 32, Item 8)
    - Charles Goodyear Medal from American Chemical Society, 1988; cuid3495 (Box 32, Item 9)
    - The Elliott Cresson Medal of the Franklin Institute, 1966-10-19; cuid3496 (Box 32, Item 10)
    - Certificate of Appreciation from Council of Long Island Technical Societies, 1963-05-07; cuid3497 (Box 33, Item 1)
    - Wayne State University College of Engineering and Division of Urban Extension Certificate, Summer 1968; cuid3498 (Box 33, Item 2)
    - VOK German Certificate, 1981-12-15; cuid3499 (Box 33, Item 3)
    - Sarnia Lecture in Science of the Chemical Institute of Canada, 1967-01-11; cuid3500 (Box 33, Item 4)
    - Consortium Officinae Chemicae Celeberrimae Certificate, undated; cuid3501 (Box 33, Item 5)
    - The Wolf Foundation Prize in Chemistry, 1979; cuid3502 (Box 33, Item 6)
    - Croatian Certificate, 1974; cuid3503 (Box 33, Item 7)
    - The National Medal of Science, 1979; cuid3504 (Box 33, Item 8)
    - Ceskoslovenska Akademie Ved Certificate, 1988; cuid3505 (Box 33, Item 9)
    - Father of Polymer Chemistry Certificate from the American Chemical Society, 1985-05-03; cuid3506 (Box 34, Item 1)
    - The International Academy of Wood Science Fellowship Award, 1968-07-02; cuid3507 (Box 34, Item 2)
    - Distinguished Lecture Award from University of Massachusetts, 1984-01; cuid3508 (Box 34, Item 3)
    - National Institute of Sciences of India Honorary Fellowship Award, 1960-12; cuid3509 (Box 34, Item 4)
    - Chemical Pioneer Award from the American Institute of Chemists, 1972-05-20; cuid3510 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Albert A. Michelson Edward W. Morley Award, 1989-04-28; cuid3511 (Box 34, Item 6)
    - Certificate from Israel Plastic Society, 1975-07-13; cuid3512 (Box 34, Item 7)
    - CIRFS Certificate, 1980-09; cuid3513 (Box 34, Item 8)
    - Technik und angewandte Naturwissenschaften from Aachener und Munchener Pries, 1975-06-23; cuid3514 (Box 34, Item 9)
    - Russian Certificate, 1974; cuid3515 (Box 34, Item 10)
    - Doctor of Science Degree from University of Nottingham, 1980-07-10; cuid3516 (Box 35, Item 1)
    - Universite Claude Bernard Honorary Doctorate, 1987-09-15; cuid3517 (Box 35, Item 2)
    - El Rector Magnifico de la Universidad Autonoma de Madrid Honorary Doctorate, 1973-06-25; cuid3518 (Box 35, Item 3)
    - Universitas Longinsvlanae Doctor of Science, 1976-06-11; cuid3519 (Box 35, Item 4)
    - Die Technische Hochschule Munchen Honorary Doctor of Natural Sciences, 1960-02-24; cuid3520 (Box 35, Item 5)
    - Das Gesamtkollegium Der Technische Hochschule In Wein Honorary Doctor of Natural Sciences, 1964-11-11; cuid3521 (Box 35, Item 6)
    - Institutul Politehnic Iasi Honorary Doctorate, 1972-10-16; cuid3522 (Box 35, Item 7)
    - Institutul Politehnic "Gh. Asachi" Din Iasi Honorary Doctorate, 1971-05-29; cuid3523 (Box 35, Item 8)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Honorary Doctorate, 1965-06-09; cuid3524 (Box 35, Item 9)
    - University of Massachusetts Honorary Doctorate Paper, 1982-07-12; cuid3525 (Box 35, Item 10)
    - University of Massachusetts Honorary Doctorate, 1982-07-12; cuid3526 (Box 35, Item 11)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science Fifty Year Membership Certificate, 1989-07-28; cuid3527 (Box 36, Item 1)
    - The National Register of Prominent Americas and International Notables Certificate, 1978-1979; cuid3528 (Box 36, Item 2)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences Honorary Life Membership, undated; cuid3529 (Box 36, Item 3)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences Honorary Life Membership 1977, 1977-12-08; cuid3530 (Box 36, Item 4)
    - Honorary Membership to the Chemists Club of New York, 1976-12-29; cuid3531 (Box 36, Item 5)
    - National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America Membership Certificate, 1961-04-25; cuid3532 (Box 36, Item 6)
    - Plastics Institute of America Membership Certificate, 1965-01-22; cuid3533 (Box 36, Item 7)
    - The American Institute of Chemists Life Fellowship Certificate, 1978-04-13; cuid3534 (Box 36, Item 8)
    - Honorary Membership to the Society for the Chemical Industry, 1980-10-29; cuid3535 (Box 36, Item 9)
    - Japanese Certificate, 1972-05-25; cuid3536 (Box 36, Item 10)
    - Austrian Academy of Science Honorary Membership of the Mathmatical and Natural Science Class, 1970-05-26; cuid3537 (Box 36, Item 11)
    - Polytechnic University Establishment of the Alstadt, Lord, Mark Chair in the Natural Sciences, 1989-02-21; cuid3538 (Box 36, Item 12)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York President's Associates Membership, 1982-10-06; cuid3539 (Box 36, Item 13)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Presentation of Bust, 1960-03-12; cuid3540 (Box 36, Item 14)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Presentation of Bust, 1960-03-12; cuid3541 (Box 36, Item 15)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Retirement Letter, 1965-06-03; cuid3542 (Box 36, Item 16)
    - Wiener Beiting May 3, 1895 Copy, undated; cuid3543 (Box 37, Item 1)
    - The New York Times May 3, 1895 Copy, undated; cuid3544 (Box 37, Item 2)
    - The White House Correspondence from Ronald Reagan, 1985-04-24; cuid3545 (Box 37, Item 3)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York Certificate of Appreciation, 1974-05-03; cuid3546 (Box 37, Item 4)
    - 80th Birthday Recognition from the Polish Academy of Science, 1975; cuid3547 (Box 37, Item 5)
    - 80th Birthday Recognition from Cristofor Simionescu, 1975; cuid3548 (Box 37, Item 6)
    - 80th Birthday Recognition from S.R. Palit from High Polymer Laboratory at IACS, 1975-04-15; cuid3549 (Box 37, Item 7)
    - 80th Birthday Recognition from Specialist Group for Macromolecular Chemistry, 1975; cuid3550 (Box 37, Item 8)
    - 80th Birthday Recognition from IUPAC Symposium on Macromolecules, 1975; cuid3551 (Box 37, Item 9)
    - Charles Goodyear Medal from American Chemical Society, 1988; cuid3552 (Box 38, Item 1)
    - Wooden plaque backing, undated; cuid3553 (Box 38, Item 2)
  - Subseries C: Needs Conservation
    Conditions Governing Access
    Items in this subseries need conservation and have limited access.